Okay,it's done.
好 搞定了
Look,guys, for the future,I don't
mind killing the big spiders,
听着 男同胞们
我不介意以后替你们干掉大蜘蛛
but you have to at least
try with the little ones.
但小的你们总得自己来吧
Penny,please.
Penny 别说了
We're facing a far more serious
problem than stray arachnids.
这问题可比迷路严重得多
- Sheldon,it's not so bad.
- Not bad? It's horrible.
- Sheldon 没有那么糟
- 不糟? 简直是恐怖!
I mean,you hear stories about this sort of
thing, but you never think it'll happen to you.
这种事时常听到
但啥时候想到会发生在自己身上
So they steamed your
dumplings. Get over it.
他们是坏了你的饺子 算了吧
New topic,please.
换个新话题吧
All right,Penny.
好 Penny
Let me take this opportunity to point out that
you are looking particularly ravishing today.
那就让我借此机会说出
你今天可真是迷死人啊
Not with a thousand condoms, Howard.
戴上一千个安全套再说吧 Howard
So,there is a number.
这么说 还有个数呢
Okay,new topic,please.
够了 换个新话题吧
Hey,did you hear the people
upstairs in 5A are moving out?
嘿 你们听说5楼A座的人要搬出去了吗?
- No,shh-shh-shh!
- What?
- 不 嘘-嘘-嘘!
- 虾~米?
- The people upstairs are moving out.
- No!
- 楼上的人要搬走了
- 不!
The horror...
骇人听闻...
Why would you just say
something like that?
你为什么要这样说话?
No,no,no, no,no,no,no...
不不不...
How else was I supposed to say it?
那我还能怎么个说法?
Slowly. Like putting a new fish in
a tank. You don't just drop it in.
有点铺垫嘛 就像把金鱼放进鱼缸
不是一下子就把它扔进去吧
You let the bag sit
in the water a while.
你得把袋子在水里放一会儿
The horror...
骇人听闻...
Sheldon,I'm sure it's going to be fine.
Sheldon 我肯定会没事的
No,it's not going to be
fine. Change is never fine.
不 怎么可能没事 改变从来不会没事
They say it is, but it's not.
人们这么说 但事实并非如此
Okay,honey,did you even know
the people that are moving out?
亲爱的 你认识那些要搬走的人么?
I never met them. That's
what made them perfect.
我从没见过他们 所以他们才如此完美
There were no awkward
"hellos" in the halls.
不用尴尬地在走廊里打招呼
There's no clickety-clacking of
high heel shoes on hardwood floors.
没有硬木地板上咔嗒咔嗒的高跟鞋声
They may as well have been a family of cats
just jumping around from drape to drape.
他们也可能是一窝猫
在帘子间跳来跳去
Without that annoying
ammonia urine smell.
但他们没有烦人的尿骚味
Well,I'm sure the new
people will be just as quiet.
我肯定新来的人也会同样安静的
You can't know that. How
can you possibly know that?
你又不知道 这你要怎么知道?
You're right,I can't. You know what?
你说得没错 我不知道 你知道吗?
Anyone could rent that apartment now:
an opera singer, the cast ofStomp...
谁都有可能租下那间公寓
歌剧演员 街舞少年剧组的...
Yeah,a tap-dancing
pirate with a wooden leg.
对哈 装着个木腿踢踏舞演员
Why are you making it worse?
你为什么要越搞越僵?
I tried making it better.
He wouldn't go for it.
我想往好的方面说 可他不听啊
You're right! That's a great idea.
没错! 那是个好主意
- What?
- I'll take the apartment upstairs.
- 什么?
- 我要租下楼上的公寓
I can finally get away from my mother and
we can all spend some more time together.
我终于可以离我妈远远的了
我们也能有多一点时间在一起了
If you catch my drift.
如果你明白我的意思的话
The horror...
骇人听闻...
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 饭特稀 奕鹂
校对: 潘小妮
时间轴: 咔肉肉
双语:徐小帆
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode19
天才理论传
第二季 第19集
Hold on.You honestly
expect me to believe
等等 你们真的以为我会相信
that social protocol dictates we
break our backs helping Wolowitz move,
礼节上我们这么拼命替Wolowitz搬家
and then he only need buy us a pizza?
他只需要买个匹萨给我们吃?
I'm sorry,that really is how it works.
抱歉 不过事实就是如此
You' tricking me.
你们在耍我
You tell me the truth, what do we get?
给我说实话 我们到底有什么好处?
Raj,help me out here.
Raj 帮帮忙吧
You get to choose between
a mountain bike or a PS3.
你可以在山地车和PS3之间选一个
I knew it!
我就知道!
PS3,definitely PS3.
PS3 绝对是PS3了
Who would pick a mountain bike?
谁会选山地车啊?
Enough with the guilt,Ma.
We'll still see each other.
别再让我有负罪感了 老妈
我们还是会再见的
I'll come over every night
and have dinner with you.
我会每晚过来和你共进晚餐的
The hell you will!
吃你个大头鬼!
What am I running here,
a fancy restaurant?
你把这儿当什么地方了? 高级餐厅?
Does this look like Olive Garden?
看着像橄榄树花园(意式餐厅)么?
Okay,I get it, you're angry.
好吧 我了解了 你生气了
You don't want to see your
little bird leave the nest.
你不愿见到你的小鸟飞离巢穴
"Little bird"? You're almost 30!
"小鸟"? 你都快30了!
Fly,for God's sake!
飞吧 我的神呐!
Fine,I'll stay! Ya happy,crazy lady?
好 我不搬! 开心了吧 疯婆子?
I sure as hell hope so,
because you're ruing my life!
我打心底里这么想
因为你毁了我的生活!
Hey,Penny? It's Leonard.
嘿 是Penny吗? 我是Leonard
Good news,you can take
your head out of the oven.
好消息 你可以把脑袋从烤炉里拿出来了
I guess I won't be needing this.
我想我也不需要这玩意儿了
Oh,no...
噢 不...
Thenewones.
新来的
They're here.
已经到了
Stay calm. We don't know
anything about them yet.
别冲动 我们还对他们一无所知
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
I'm checking for musical instruments.
我在检查有没有乐器
Does that sound like castanets to you?
你觉得这个听起来像响板么?
- The box says "kitchen."
- So?
- 盒子上写着"厨具"
- 那又怎样?
Do cocaine smugglers
write "cocaine" on the box?
毒贩子会在盒子上写"可卡因"么?
- Hello?
- Hello.
- 你好
I'm Alicia. I'm moving in upstairs.
我是Alicia 我要搬进楼上了
That is so great.
真是太棒了
Oh,I'm Leonard. I live downstairs.
噢 我是Leonard 我住在楼下
Upstairs from here, but under you.
在这儿上头 不过在你下面
Not under you per se,
but under your apartment.
实际上不是在你下面
而是在你的公寓下面
- That's nice.
- Yeah,it is.
- 真不错
- 是啊
If that concludes your
faltering attempt to mate...
求爱呢啊 结巴完了换我说
- Hello.
- 你好
On a scale of one to ten, how light
of foot would you describe yourself,
一到十 你给自己脚步声定个级别
with one being not cat-like at
all,and ten being freakishly feline?
一代表完全不像猫类
十代表简直就是猫科动物
"Freakishly feline"?
"简直就是猫科动物"?
Is that your answer or do you
not understand the question?
这是你的答案还是你没听懂问题?
- We'll come back to that one.
- Sheldon...
- 这个待会再说
Hang on. Are you now or have you ever
been a salsa,Irish folk or break-dancer?
等等 你现在或曾经跳过萨尔萨舞
爱尔兰民舞或者街舞吗?
- No.
- You're making her uncomfortable.
- 没有
- 你问得她不自在了
Oh,I'm sorry. Well,if it helps you feel
any better, you're doing very well so far.
抱歉 以表安慰 目前你做的很好
Next question: are you fertile?
下一个问题 你能生育吗?
What?
什么?
I'm trying to determine whether crying
infants above my head are a possibility.
我想知道以后楼上会不会有哭闹的婴儿
I have no immediate plans.
目前没有打算
If that changes, let me know.
如果有 告诉我
And finally,area rugs, pro or con?
那最后 小地毯 赞成还是反对?
- Pro?
- Alicia?
- 赞成?
- Yes?
- Welcome to the building.
- 什么事?
- 欢迎来到这里
Thanks so much for helping me,Leonard.
多谢你帮忙 Leonard
Thank you so much for giving
me the opportunity to help.
多谢你给我这个机会
Oh,hey,guys.
噢 你们好啊
Hey,Penny. This is
Alicia,our new neighbor.
嘿 Penny 这是我们的新邻居 Alicia
I'm helping.
我在帮忙
I can see.
看见了
Alicia's non-musical,
childless and pro-rug.
Alicia不玩音乐 不生孩子 赞成小地毯
She's still on probation,
of course, but I ke her.
当然她还在试用期 不过我喜欢她
Cool T-shirt.
好酷的T恤啊
Oh,yeah,I don't usually dress
like this. I'm going jogging.
噢 是啊 我通常不这么打扮
这正要去慢跑呢
- You don't jog.
- I can start.
- 你又不慢跑的
- 这不正要开始么
True,but the more likely explanation for your
attire is that you're out of clean clothes again.
那是 不过更合理的解释是
你又没有干净的衣服穿了
- Thank you,Sheldon.
- You're welcome,Penny.
- 谢谢侬 Sheldon
- 不客气 Penny
Please,you look cute. I'm
dressed like a slob today,too.
得了吧 你看上去多可爱
我今天也穿得像邋遢鬼似的
I think you look fantastic.
我觉得你看起来棒极了
This one's a player,huh?
这家伙棒极了 哈?
Oh,yeah,be careful.
噢 是啊 要小心
- Thanks for the warning.
- Okay.
- 多谢提醒
- 好
- I'll see you around.
- See ya.
- 回见了
- 再见
I'm dressed like a slob today,too.
我今天也穿得像邋遢鬼似的
Oh,micry. I enjoy micry.
噢 模仿 我爱模仿
I've been working on Admiral
Ackbar fromReturn of the Jedi.
我一直在模仿"绝地武士归来"的阿克巴
"It's a trap."
"这是个陷阱"
You have to imagine me
with a giant squid head.
你得想象我有个巨大的鱿鱼脑袋
"It's a trap."
"这是个陷阱"
Come.
进来
Congratulations, I see
you did your laundry.
恭喜啊 你衣服洗好了
Well,sort of.
呃 算是吧
- How does one "sort of..."
- I bought new clothes,okay?
- 要怎么"算是..."呢?
- 我买了新衣服 好了吧?
Is Leonard around?
Leonard在吗?
He's upstairs at Alicia's.
他在楼上Alicia那儿
All right, that's cool,no biggie.
好吧 没事 没什么大不了
He said he'd help me set up my
printer, but I guess I can wait.
他说他会帮我装打印机的
不过我想我可以等等
What exactly is he doing up there?
他究竟在上头干什么呢?
In what I can only perceive as
a tactical move to destroy me,
我只能理解为是
用来摧毁我的战术性行动
he is with Wolowitz and
Koothrappali setting up her stereo.
他和Wolowitz还有Koothrappali
在帮她装立体声系统
Oh,they're all up
there,huh? Hmm,typical.
噢 他们都在上头 哈? 典型啊
It's axiomatically atypical.
显然非典型啊
Up until recently, they did not know Alicia, and
had no encounters with her in a previous location.
直到最近 他们还不认识Alicia
以前也没有在哪儿见过她
They never went upstairs
to visit the former tenants,
他们从来不上楼去看以前的房客
so your characterization of their behavior
as "typical" is demonstrably fallacious.
所以你将他们的行为归为"典型"
显然是谬论
Okay,now I see the giant squid head.
好了 现在我看见巨型鱿鱼脑袋了
Oh,great! Now,I have
to start all over again.
这下好了! 我得从头再来一遍
Yeah,I thought about
renting this apartment,
没错 我还想租下这间公寓呢
but I'm really more of a
"downtown loft" kind of guy.
但我更喜欢住"市区阁楼"
Cool. So are you in a loft now?
真酷 那么说你现在住阁楼咯?
Oh,actually,I'm,uh,living
with a woman in Altadena.
噢 实际上 我现在和一个女人
一起住在Altadena
Purely platonic. She's also my maid.
纯柏拉图式的 她也是我的女仆
Sounds like a sweet deal.
听起来不错啊
I won't lie. It's pretty dope.
不骗你哦 挺无聊的
Hello?
嗨
Hey,I just wanted to bring
you a little housewarming gift.
嘿 我想给你带来点乔迁之喜的薄礼
That is so sweet. Come
on in. Let's open it.
你太贴心了 快进来吧 我们打开尝尝
- Great.
- Nice dress.
- 好极了
- 裙子很漂亮
Oh,this? I'm dressed like a slob today.
哦 这条?我今天穿得像邋遢鬼似的
The guys have been helping
me set up my sound system.
他们在帮我组装音响系统
I've never had such
good-looking technical support.
我从未见过这么靓的技术人员
Oh,pish-posh.
噢 哪里哪里
I don't know, it means shucks.
管它呢 就是不咋靓的意思呗
"Shucks" means shucks.
Let one go once in a while.
不靓就是不靓嘛 您老别总那么较真成不
- Hey,uh,Penny,you want to hear something awesome?
- Yeah.
- Penny 有个消息很赞 想听不?
- 说啊
Alicia is an actress, just like you.
Alicia是名演员 和你一样
That is so awesome.
真太赞了
Well,trying to be, but it's so hard.
努力做演员 但真的很难啊
Yeah,I know,tell me about it.
我了解 还用说嘛
I've been out here three months,
我已经来这儿三个月了
and all I've gotten is a couple of national
commercials and this recurring thing on a soap.
只不过接了几个商业广告
和一部肥皂剧的循环角色
That's why I work at the Cheesecake
Factory. I'm holding out for the right part.
所以我一直在在"酪饼工厂"工作
就是在等好角色啊
Alicia,what do you want as your default
setting for DVDs,5. 1 Dolby or DTS?
Alicia 你要怎样的DVD默认设置
杜比5.1还是DTS?
Whatever you think is best,cutie.
你认为哪个好就设置哪个吧 靓仔
Well,DTS has more low end,so...
DTS有更多低档环绕扬声器 所以...
Okay.
好吧
Uh,hey,guys,guys, you will
really appreciate this.
嘿 伙计们 这个你们肯定爱听
I read the best science
joke on the Internet.
我在网上读到个爆笑科学笑话
Alicia,you won't get it, but
it's right up their alley.
Alicia 你不会理解的 但很对他们胃口
Anyway,so, this physicist goes
into an ice cream parlor every week
就是说呢 有个物理学家
每周都会去一家冰淇淋店
and orders an ice cream
sundae for himself,
给他自己点一份冰淇淋圣代
and then offers one to the
empty stool sitting next to him.
然后给他旁边的空位点一份
This goes on for a while until the
owner finally asks him what he's doing.
这情况持续了一段时间
直到最后老板问他在干嘛
The man says, "Well,I'm a
physicist, "and quantum mechanics...
那家伙说 "我是个物理学家
而量子力学呢..."
teaches us "that it is possible
for the matter above this stool
"告诉我们这位子上的物体有可能"
"to spontaneously turn into a beautiful woman who
might accept my offer and fall in love with me."
"自然地转化成一个漂亮的姑娘
接受我的请客并与我坠入爱河"
The owner then says, "Well,lots of single,
"beautiful women come in here ever day.
老板说"这儿每天有很多单身美女客人"
"Why don't you buy an ice cream for one of
them, and they might fall in love with you?"
"你干嘛不给其中一位买份冰淇淋呢
她们也许会与你坠入爱河啊"
And the physicist says, "Yeah,but
what are the odds of that happening?"
物理学家答道
"是啊 但又有多大可能呢?"
It's a little insulting,
don't you think?
这笑话有点伤人 不是吗?
How would I know? I'm
not even sure I get it.
我怎么知道? 我都不确定我是不是真懂了
Hey,Leonard?
嘿 Leonard
If you're done with the DVD
player, can you set up my printer?
你要是弄完了DVD播放机
能帮我装下打印机吗?
Uh,yeah,I'd love to.
噢 好的 我很乐意
Uh,hey,maybe when you're done with
her printer,you could set up mine.
嘿 也许等你弄完了她的打印机
能再帮我装一下我的
You know,like you
promised... a week ago.
你知道的 你一周前就...答应了
Yeah,I'll get to
it-- don't nag me.
好的 我会去装的 别催我
Hello there.
嗨
Who is it?
是哪位?
Oh hello,Penny.
It's open-- come in.
你好 Penny 门是开的 请进
Sarcasm.
讽刺吧
Well,they're all still up there.
他们还在楼上
You think I can't hear them?
你以为我听不到?
Listen to that: stomp,stomp,stomp.
听 咚 咚 咚
That's Wolowitz in his
stacked heels that fool no one.
傻子都知道是Wolowitz那
婀娜小脚在走来走去
I don't even know why
I care. I don't care.
我都不知道我为什么要在乎
我才不在乎呢
All right,I cared enough to memorize
that stupid joke, but that's all I care.
好吧 我在乎到去背那个愚蠢的笑话
但我就在乎这个而已
You know,Penny, there's something that
occurs in beehives you might find interesting.
知道吗 Penny 蜂窝里的事你也许会感兴趣
Occasionally, a new queen will arrive
while the old queen is still in power.
有时 在老蜂后仍掌权时
会有一个新蜂后到来
When this happens, the old queen
must either locate to a new hive
这种情形下 老蜂后要么移居到一个新蜂窝
or engage in a battle to the
death until only one queen remains.
要么拼死一搏
直到只有一个蜂后存活下来
What are you saying, that
I'm threatened by Alicia?
你什么意思 我受到Alicia的威胁了吗?
That I'm like the old queen of the
hive and it's just time for me to go?
我就像那个蜂窝的老蜂后
是时候要我离开了?
I'm just talking about bees.
我只是在谈论蜜蜂啊
They're on The Discovery Channel.
探索频道里播的
What areyou talking about?
你在说什么呢?
Bees.
蜜蜂咯
I just got that physicist joke.
我终于明白那物理学家笑话了
Gee,Penny,thanks for buying us dinner.
哇 Penny 谢谢你给我们买晚餐
Yeah,what's the occasion?
是啊 有何事相求?
No,no occasion-- just felt like
getting some Chinese chow for my peeps.
没什么相求
只想给我的小鹬鸟们买些中国食物
Did you remember to ask for the
chicken with broccoli to be diced,
你记得要求鸡肉里的蔬菜切成块吗?
- not shredded?
- Yes.
- 不是切碎
- 是
- Even though the menu description specifies shredded?
- Yes.
- 即使菜单上说是切碎?
- 是
- Brown rice,not white?
- Yes.
- 糙米 不是白米?
- 是
- You stop at the Korean grocery and get the good hot mustard?
- Yes.
- 你到韩食店买了上等的热芥末?
- 是
- Did you pick up the low-sodium
soy sauce from the market? - Yes.
- 在超市里买了低钠的酱?
- 是
Good.
很好
See how it's done, Leonard?
瞧就是要这样 明白不 Leonard?
So,what do we got going on tonight,huh?
我们今晚做什么好呢 嗯?
Playing Halo watchingBattlestar,
drop some Mentos in Diet Coke?
玩光晕 看
还是玩健怡可乐里放薄荷糖?
You want to watchBattlestar?
你想看?
What can I say? I got my geek on,boys.
我能怎么说呢?
伙计们 我的极客细胞活跃起来了
No,no,PMS is different.
不 不是 经前综合症不这样
Oh,thank God you're home. I need help.
哦 谢天谢地你在家 我需要帮助
What's wrong?
怎么了?
I just got a callback to audition
forCSI to play a hooker who gets killed.
我刚收到CSI试演的回复
扮演一个被杀害的妓女
Oh,I'd watch that.
哦 我会看的
But my car is in the shop, and I
have to be at Universal in 45 minutes.
但我的车在店里
我得在45分钟内赶到环球影城
Okay,well,I'll take you.
好吧 那我载你去
Oh,you're a lifesaver.
哦 你真是救世主
I'll run lines with you in the car.
我和你一起坐车去
Great. And afterward, I'll
take you all out for Chinese.
太好了 之后我请你们大伙儿吃中国菜
Oh,actually,that's
okay. We already have...
其实 没关系 我们已经...
- Yum.
- Starving.
- 好耶
- 饿得不行了
Chinese food right here.
正在吃中国菜
They're gone,Penny. They can't hear you.
他们走了 Penny 听不到你的话
I cannot believe they're letting
her just use them like that.
真不敢相信他们就这样任凭她利用他们
I mean,anything she wants,they go
panting after her like trained dogs.
我意思是 不管她要什么
他们都像她训练的狗一样听从她
You know that just last week, she had
Howard drive all the way to her uncle's house
知道吗 上周 她要Howard
一直开车载她到她的叔叔家
in Orange County to pick up her TV?
就为了去橘子郡取她的电视机?
You once had Leonard and me get your
television from your ex-boyfriend.
你曾叫Leonard和我
去你的前男友家取电视机
Apples and oranges here, Sheldon.
这俩地儿能比啊 Sheldon
I'm telling you, that girl is a user,
skating through life on her looks,
我告诉你 那女的喜欢利用别人
靠她的脸蛋儿招摇过市
taking advantage of innocent, weak-willed men,
getting auditions for stupid network shows.
利用那些天真 意志薄弱的男人
得到那些愚蠢电视剧的试演
It just creams my corn.
跟她势不两立
- May I interject something here?
- Please.
- 我能插一句吗?
- 说吧
You got the wrong mustard.
你买错了芥末
Guess what? I got the part onCSI.
猜怎么着?我得到CSI那个角色了
Oh,boy.
哦 好家伙
Something wrong?
有什么不对劲吗?
Uh,no. No,no,no,you
know, congratulations.
哦 没有 没有 恭喜你
I think you'll make a great hooker.
相信你扮妓女一定很棒
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey,I got to ask you something.
嘿 我要问你些事
How much do physicists make?
物理学家能挣多少?
Um,I don't know. I don't think a lot.
呃 我不知道 我想不太多吧
Yeah,that's what I figured.
嗯 我也这么想
Well,got to run. The guys promised to set up
my satellite dish and paint my bedroom. Yay!
得走了 他们答应帮我装电视天线
粉刷卧室呢 耶!
Um,hey,hey,can I talk to
you about that for a second?
嘿嘿 我能跟你说一句吗?
About what?
说什么?
Well,you know, it's just that Leonard and
Howard and Raj, they aren't like other guys.
你知道的 Leonard Howard还有Raj
他们和别的家伙不一样
They're special.
他们很特别
Okay,they're special... and?
好的 他们很特别...还有呢?
Oh,let's see. How can I explain this?
这么说吧 我要怎么解释好呢?
Um,they don't know how
to use their shields.
他们不知道如何使用他们的盾
Shields?
盾?
Yeah,you know, like inStar Trek, when
you're in battle and you raise the shields?
是的 就像>里的
当你要战斗时 你要举起你的盾
Where the hell'd that come from?
这想法从哪儿冒出来的?
Anyways,um, you know how
guys like this are,so...
反正呢 你知道像他们这样的人...
please don't take advantage of them.
请不要利用他们
Who says I'm taking advantage of them?
谁说我在利用他们?
Come on. They're doing everything for
you, because you're leading them on.
拜托 他们为你做任何事
因为是你在引诱他们
So I let them do stuff for me.
我让他们帮我做事
They're happy. I get stuff. Who cares?
他们乐意 我事也办成了 谁有意见呢?
And how's it any
different from what you do?
这和你做的又有什么区别呢?
Excuse me?
你说什么?
I've seen you around them.
我见过你在他们旁边的样子
Are you pretending like you
don't do the exact same thing?
你想假装你没做和我同样的事吗?
Okay,lady,you areway out of line.
好吧 女士 你越轨了
Oh,I'm out of line?
是吗 我越轨了?
Yeah,you're out of line.
是的 你越过界了
Well,what are you going
to do about it... bitch?
那你打算怎么办呢...婊子?
I like Green Lantern.
我喜欢绿灯侠
I'm just saying it's pretty lame that
he can be defeated by the color yellow.
我只是觉得他能被黄色物体击倒
这一点很没说服力
Only the modern Green Lantern
is vulnerable to yellow.
黄色只对现代绿灯侠有用
Golden age Green Lantern
was vulnerable to wood.
黄金时代的绿灯侠害怕木头
Great,so I can take them both
out with a number-two pencil?
好极了 那我可以只用一支2号铅笔
就击倒他们两代了
Oh,my God! Girl fight!
哦 上帝啊 女生掐架了!
What are you doing?
你要干嘛?
I know you. You're stupid
enough to break it up.
我了解你 你会傻到要去劝架
May I say you look very comely tonight?
能允许我说 你今晚看起来很清秀吗?
Thank you.
谢谢
You're right,this filly's been broken.
你说得对 这小姑娘给打蔫了
You set it on DTS, didn't you?
你设置成DTS了 是不是?
I had to. She called me "cutie."
我没办法啊 她叫我"靓仔"
According to Alicia's Facebook page,
Alicia的facebook博客上写
she's hooking up with one
of the producers onCSI.
她跟CSI的一个制作人搞上了
Well,dead whore on TV,
live one in real life.
电视里的死妓女 现实中的活妓女
Oh,great.
哦 这下好了
Now she's jumping up
and down on the bed.
开始在床上跳上跳下了
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
天才理论传
第二季 第19集 完